 
(a) How many commits have been done to the repository?
14

(b) When was the .gitignore file modified last?
2024-09-23 18:14:38 -0500

(c) What command(s) could you use to obtain the list of files that were in a
repository on a specific date e.g., Files in the repository on 06/01/2020
git rev-list -1 --before="2020-06-01"


(d) How many times was each of the files inside the src folder modified?
There is no src folder in the repository, so there are no modification counts available for files in that directory.

(e) How many addition operations were involved in the creation of the file RE-
MOVE.txt?
The file REMOVE.txt does not exist in the repository, so there are no addition operations to report for that file.


(f) What is the difference between git log and git status?
git log shows the commit history of the repository, listing previous commits, dates and the authors, while git status shows the current state of the directory and staging area, listing changes that are staged or unstaged.

(g) What does the command shortlog do?
git shortlog summarizes git log output, grouping commits by author and providing an overview of contributions with commit messages.

(h) What command would you use to list the commits in which the file “Main.java”
was part of the committed files?
git log -- Main.java


(i) What command would you use to list the commits in which the file “Main.java”
was part of the committed files, including renames and the diffs of each com-
mit?
git log --follow -p -- Main.java


(j) What command would you use to list the commits whose commit message
contains the word “account”?
git log --grep="account"


(k) What command would you use to see the commits made by a specific person?
git log --author="Author Name"


(l) What command would you use to see the commits made by “Lauren” between
01/05/2014 and 01/14/2024?
git log --author="Lauren" --since="2014-01-05" --until="2024-01-14"




